dark glasses,
let me think,
let's assume weave low cost,
little box to climb.
What would the cart do?
Well,
first your brand is down here,
then try to think climbing step by step,
I don't know,
an influencer named João is going there,
you will do what you will ask there
advertise my glasses for free,
I give you the glasses in exchange for advertising,
in return,
no,
don't do that,
man,
doesn't do that,
will think your glasses call bronx,
which was my brand name,
when you go to send a message you will send it,
hello,
my name is Deise,
I want to give you a pair of glasses as a gift,
won't you tell him like that?
Hello John,
all right?
My name is Deisencelos and I am the CEO
of the bronx sangs.
We have a new line of and
has a blah blah coated finish
and na na na na!
And you talk about the specifications of your glasses
Do you value your product?
The reason for my contact is because
I'm selecting people I admire
and have good taste.
that's why
please
I request your address here so that I can send
it's like present,
a box of our products for you to discover.
Grateful for your attention,
thoughtfully,
sincencelos took out,
spoke to the person as important,
said she has good taste,
is giving her a gift,
Yes?
It was,
isn't it what?
You do,
but how do you succeed?